<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tutorials on Wear Gallery</title><link>https://weargallery.app/en/docs/tutorials/</link><description>Recent content in Tutorials on Wear Gallery</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://weargallery.app/en/docs/tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Compatibility</title><link>https://weargallery.app/en/docs/tutorials/compatibility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://weargallery.app/en/docs/tutorials/compatibility/</guid><description>Wear Gallery is not compatible with all Huawei phones!
Supported OS on watch # Wear OS 2.x and above Samsung Galaxy Watch 4+ (Wear OS version) Ticwear Start with v6.1, live-previews for Ticwear are no longer supported. There is no need for Ticwear-only users to install the mobile client. Unofficially supported watches # It may work, but you can&amp;rsquo;t get preview in real time, just install the watch side and use the LAN transfer:</description></item><item><title>Install</title><link>https://weargallery.app/en/docs/tutorials/install/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://weargallery.app/en/docs/tutorials/install/</guid><description>Release channel # The official release channels of wear gallery are:
Github Release Google Play Mobvoi App Store (watch client) Please do not install from unofficial sources, as this may put your device at risk. Install # Watch client # Please install from the app store on your watch as the easiest, fastest and safest solution. If your watch does not have an app store or you cannot find the wear gallery, please download the apk package directly from the distribution channel above and install it to your watch using ADB.</description></item><item><title>Live Preview</title><link>https://weargallery.app/en/docs/tutorials/live-preview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://weargallery.app/en/docs/tutorials/live-preview/</guid><description>Basic requirements # The Wear Gallery supports live preview of images in your phone, but only if you meet the requirements below. If you can&amp;rsquo;t meet the requirements or don&amp;rsquo;t want to use this feature, you can hide it in the settings.
Your mobile phone runs on Android OS and the Wear Gallery must be installed on your phone. The watch is paired with the phone and connected via Bluetooth.</description></item><item><title>Batch Sending</title><link>https://weargallery.app/en/docs/tutorials/batch-sending/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://weargallery.app/en/docs/tutorials/batch-sending/</guid><description>Starting with v6.1, the mobile client is focused on serving the watch and no longer comes standard with picture viewing. For speed and stability reasons, if you need to transfer a large number of, or FHD pictures at once, it is highly recommended to use a LAN transfer rather than relying on Bluetooth to send them in bulk. Open any app (system album is recommended), select all the pictures you want to send, click &amp;ldquo;Share&amp;rdquo;, and select &amp;ldquo;Send to Watch&amp;rdquo; in the pop-up list.</description></item></channel></rss>